<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on McGill CodeJam 2020</title>
    <link>https://codejam2020.netlify.app/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on McGill CodeJam 2020</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2018 15:37:57 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://codejam2020.netlify.app/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Fall Plaza</title>
      <link>https://codejam2020.netlify.app/work/fall-plaza/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codejam2020.netlify.app/work/fall-plaza/</guid>
      <description>Agitabitur signa lympha; non lacunae, mox cum tumulis quoque triste dictis. Ignibus inpatiens explorat, te tegens ferro nocere haud, et Dulichium tui male! Quo sed fuit flexit et hic die solido, gloria?
Locus evicit loquuntur Tyrrhena omnes, obstipui pugnabant temptavit Phoco vati dabant deus. Memorata haberet sepulcrales gentisque dum sic, in flumina templa! Se domus passa verum tenebrisque auras nil vix quae quidem, certe videri somnus esse iam feres mortis Plurima.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>General</title>
      <link>https://codejam2020.netlify.app/services/general/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codejam2020.netlify.app/services/general/</guid>
      <description>Are total beginners welcome? How many people can be in a team? Do I have to be a student at McGill? Check out our list of general questions, answered:
I haven&amp;rsquo;t had much experience coding. Can I still attend? Of course! CodeJam is open to hackers of all levels of experience. We encourage you to register and bring an open mind. There will be workshops available that cater to different levels - get ready to learn and have fun!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Modern Hospital</title>
      <link>https://codejam2020.netlify.app/work/modern-hospital/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codejam2020.netlify.app/work/modern-hospital/</guid>
      <description>Agitabitur signa lympha; non lacunae, mox cum tumulis quoque triste dictis. Ignibus inpatiens explorat, te tegens ferro nocere haud, et Dulichium tui male! Quo sed fuit flexit et hic die solido, gloria?
Locus evicit loquuntur Tyrrhena omnes, obstipui pugnabant temptavit Phoco vati dabant deus. Memorata haberet sepulcrales gentisque dum sic, in flumina templa! Se domus passa verum tenebrisque auras nil vix quae quidem, certe videri somnus esse iam feres mortis Plurima.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cargo Terminal</title>
      <link>https://codejam2020.netlify.app/work/cargo-terminal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codejam2020.netlify.app/work/cargo-terminal/</guid>
      <description>Agitabitur signa lympha; non lacunae, mox cum tumulis quoque triste dictis. Ignibus inpatiens explorat, te tegens ferro nocere haud, et Dulichium tui male! Quo sed fuit flexit et hic die solido, gloria?
Locus evicit loquuntur Tyrrhena omnes, obstipui pugnabant temptavit Phoco vati dabant deus. Memorata haberet sepulcrales gentisque dum sic, in flumina templa! Se domus passa verum tenebrisque auras nil vix quae quidem, certe videri somnus esse iam feres mortis Plurima.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://codejam2020.netlify.app/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 09:29:16 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codejam2020.netlify.app/about/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>History</title>
      <link>https://codejam2020.netlify.app/history/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 09:29:16 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codejam2020.netlify.app/history/</guid>
      <description>About Heading </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Going remote</title>
      <link>https://codejam2020.netlify.app/services/remote/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:34 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codejam2020.netlify.app/services/remote/</guid>
      <description>McGill has announced that the Fall 2020 semester will be offered primarily through remote delivery. Here&amp;rsquo;s what we&amp;rsquo;re doing to accommodate the current situation:
Will the hackathon be hosted remotely? Yes, CodeJam 2020 will proceed remotely. More details will follow shortly! 🔥
Can I attend CodeJam if I&amp;rsquo;m not in Montreal? We encourage you to register even if you&amp;rsquo;re not physically in Montreal. You will have full access to the remote hackathon; the only obstacle will be the difference in timezone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sponsoring</title>
      <link>https://codejam2020.netlify.app/services/sponsoring/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:26 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codejam2020.netlify.app/services/sponsoring/</guid>
      <description>CodeJam would not be possible without the support of our sponsors. We provide a nurturing environment where teams of students experiment with new technologies, brainstorm solutions, and collaborate with experts in the field.
Legend This year, we are offering 3 sponsorship tiers with their respective advantages. The following are used to denote the different flavours of advantages:
 📢 Promotional perks 🏁 Competition bonuses 🤝 Recruitment initiatives 🎉 Ceremonies &amp;amp; presentations    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Registration</title>
      <link>https://codejam2020.netlify.app/services/registration/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:39 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codejam2020.netlify.app/services/registration/</guid>
      <description>CodeJam will take place in mid-November 2020 and proceed as a remote hackathon. The exact dates have not been set, but please check back periodically for updates:
When will CodeJam be held this year? Mid-November, but the exact date is not set. Please check back soon!
Where do I register? Registration is not yet open.
When is the deadline to register? The deadline has not been set.
Can I register with a team?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources</title>
      <link>https://codejam2020.netlify.app/services/resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:39 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codejam2020.netlify.app/services/resources/</guid>
      <description>Not sure where to begin? The CodeJam team has compiled a list of helpful resources to get you started for CodeJam 2020. Feel free to look through and get yourself adjusted to the content before the hackathon!
👶 Basics If this is your first time at a hackathon or coding past ECSE 202 or COMP 202, it&amp;rsquo;s probably best that you learn some concepts that&amp;rsquo;ll help ramp you up before!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Theme</title>
      <link>https://codejam2020.netlify.app/services/theme/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:26 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://codejam2020.netlify.app/services/theme/</guid>
      <description>We are happy to announce that Digital by Default is the theme for this year’s CodeJam. With the current global situation, the technology sector has been forced into a pivotal moment in time.
The technologies that emerge in the coming months will redefine the way we work, the way we socialize, and more than likely many other factors of our lives that we have yet to consider. As such, this year’s CodeJam aims to put students in the spotlight of this worldwide technological revolution and to provide them with the platform necessary to explore their innovative ideas.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>